mediaondemand.net 2010-06-11

# Media On Demand - The Streaming Media and webcast Specialists - Privacy

Media On Demand is committed to responsible management of consumer data. We comply with all rules, both ethical and legal, with respect to the use of consumer information obtained by us and we adhere strictly to all industry guidelines at all times. We undertake to continuously monitor our management of the use and security of consumer information to uphold your rights. This statement outlines the type of information we collect and store, our usage policy, and whom to contact with questions or concerns.

From time to time Media On Demand may ask for and / or you may choose to submit personal data to Media On Demand (including your email address and contact details) by filling out a feedback form or otherwise by telling Media On Demand about yourself or your activities.

Media On Demand will not collect, store or process any personal information about you unless you provide it to us voluntarily.

If you do submit it, you agree and accept that this data may be used, stored and processed to develop and improve Media On Demand’s services including their operation, administration and development as well as for operational, identification, marketing, administrative, advertising and promotional purposes but only in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998.

From time to time Media On Demand may want to share this data with other reputable companies both within and outside the European Union. Media On Demand may also use the information or parts of it to occasionally broadcast it or notify you about Media On Demand events or related activities and / or services that you may find useful.

Once collected, such data will be held within the European Union and the European Economic Area or other territory complying with the legal and technical guidelines laid down for handling data by the European Union and will only be used for the specific purpose for which it was sought and to which you consented. It will not be used for any other purpose whatsoever. Any personal data we hold on you will be deleted or updated upon request and any inaccurate or misleading data held will be changed or deleted upon your request.

If you do not want Media On Demand to collect or process your personal data as described above, please do not submit it and if you have or you believe that we have data about you that is incorrect or should you wish your data to be deleted or amended for any reason please email Media On Demand at the address below and the information will be corrected as soon as possible or removed from our database as you request.

Any data supplied by you will be kept secure in accordance with the requirements of our data protection licence and with the directions of the Data Protection Commissioner through whom this licence is held.

Details of the data we hold on you will be provided on request although we reserve the right to charge the relevant statutory disclosure fee (where appropriate). Any request of this nature should be directed to the e-mail address shown at the bottom of this notice. 

As required by the UK Data Protection Act 1998 Media On Demand follow strict security procedures in relation to the storage and disclosure of information which you have given to us, to prevent unauthorised access or use of such data. In the event, however, that Media On Demand or its officers or employees are required to undertake any act under the Regulation of Investigatory Powers Act or similar legislation Media On Demand or such person shall be entitled and occasionally obliged to do so without informing you. We would also ask that in such circumstances you co-operate with Media On Demand

## Non-personally Identifiable Information Collected Automatically

For each visitor to Media On Demand's website and associated websites, our Web server automatically recognises your domain, the type of Internet browser you are using, the type of computer operating system you are using and the domain name of the Web site from which you linked to our site. This non-personally identifiable information is collected automatically, used for internal review, then discarded.

## Who to Contact

Please e-mail questions or requests for more information about Media On Demand's privacy policies and initiatives to info@mediaondemand.net

Anyone may request the removal of his or her name from Media On Demand's mailing lists, announcement lists or marketing database by sending an e-mail to [info@mediaondemand.net](mailto:info@mediaondemand.net?subject=enquiry) You must provide your name, complete street address, city, country, post code and e-mail address. Any data we hold on you will be deleted from our existing files upon receipt of such notice.
